(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-25T09:52:45.203124",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
今日も頑張った〜
Whew~ Another hard day's work done...
気がついたら朝だし
Huh? Morning already?
めっちゃいい天気！
And the weather's actually perfect!
いいね！
Wow!
流石に疲れたな...
I'm so exhausted...
お腹すいたし
And starving.
誰かにご飯作ってもらいたいな
Honestly, someone should be making me breakfast right now.
私をお世話してくれる人いないかな〜
Surely there's someone out there willing to take care of me.
ちょっとリフレッシュするためにお散歩をして
Maybe a little walk will help me recharge.
誰か家に呼んじゃおう！
Then I'll invite someone over.
こんな時間に誰か来てくれる人いるかな？
I don't know. Who's around at this hour?
うーん ちょっと考えよ
I gotta think about this.
いたい...
Oww...
ここはどこ？
Where am I?
確か車に轢かれて...
Last thing I remember, I got hit by a car...
なんか立派な玉座があるけど
Whoa, that's a pretty fancy throne.
偉い人がいるのかな？
Does someone important live here or something?
さっきはよくも轢いてくれたな！
So you're the one who ran me over earlier!
そもそもなんで車なんか運転してたの?!
Why were you even driving a car?!
まって...
Wait...
ってか運転できたの?!
you can drive?!
そんな小さな手足で? ペダルに届くわけないでしょ！
With those tiny little arms and legs? There's no way you could even reach the pedals!
だからミスって私を轢いたんでしょ？
That's why you messed up and ran me over, isn't it?
あなたはここがどこか知らないの？
You know where we are?
なんで知らないのよ！
How do you not know?!
あなたのせいで よくわからない場所にいるのに!!
It's because of you that I'm stuck in some place I don't even recognize!!
やっと見つけた！
Finally found you!
時間の典獄クローニー！
Kronii, Warden of Time!
ここまで長い旅だった… めちゃくちゃ時間がかかった
What a long journey it's been... Took forever.
まさか 帰り方もわからないなんて言わないよね？
You're not about to tell me you don't even know how to get back home... right?
なんかめちゃ揉めてるっぽいね
They're really going at it.
私たちも混ざっちゃおうか！
Maybe we should join in too!
奇襲を仕掛けようって言うなら まぁ……いいけど でも私はいや……参加したくない
If you're saying we should sneak in and attack... sure, but I don't want to join.
でも あいつらが戦いに気を取られている間に 倒すことはできる
But we can take them down while they're distracted by fighting.
ジジ！CC！
Gigi! CC!
なんかクニーズに車で轢かれて 気がついたらここにいたんだけど！
So, one of the Kronies ran me over with a car, and when I came to, I was here!
気がついたらここにいたんだけど！
When I came to, I was here!
ここがどこだか知ってる？
Do you know where this place is?
なんで私たちのこと知ってるんだろ？
Why does she know who we are?
しかもクロニーズってなんだよ
And what's a "Kronie," anyway?
ここがどこかわかってないみたいだけど…
She doesn't seem to know where she is, but...
あの人 ここのボスのはずじゃないの？
isn't she supposed to be the boss here?
うん…
Yeah...
それに なんか弱そうだし… うん…
and she kinda looks weak... Yeah...
どうしたの…？なに？
What's going on...? What?
やっつけて 英雄になるぞ！
Let's beat her and become heroes!
はっ？！え？！
Huh?! E?!
うわっ！死ね！消えろ クズ！すぐに！
Argh! Die, scum! Die! Now!
いや それはちょっとやりすぎでしょ おい！落ち着いて ちょっと 何？
Okay, that's a little too far. Hey... Okay. You need to chill out. What?
消えろ 消えろ 消えろー
Kill her, kill her, kill her!
冗談でしょ
Don't kill me!
え？待って なに？なんで攻撃してくるの？
What? Wait. W-why are you even attacking me?
だって ここではあなたがボスなんでしょ？ 私たちは英雄になるために来たんだ！
I mean, you're the boss here, right? We came here to become heroes!
あ… そういうことね！オッケー わかった
Ah... So we're playing hero and villain. Okay. Okay, I get you.
ごっこ？ これは本物だよ！
Playing? It... It's real!
オッケー うん いいよ
Okay. Yeah, sure.
私が勝ったら ご飯作って お世話してほしいにゃ～！
Then if I win, I want you to cook for me and then take care of me, meow~!
う わ… いや 遠慮するわ
Uh-ew... I don't... No, thank you.
心配しないで 子猫ちゃん 私がお世話してあげる ははは！
Ah, don't worry, kitten. I-I'll take care of you. Ha ha ha!
うん。君のペットになんかなりたくない
Okay. I don't want to be your pet.
やぁ！！ ははは！
Oh! Ha ha ha!
弱いね
Loser!
いち？！ ははは！
One?! Ha ha ha!
1ダメージはあった ごっこ遊びにしてはさ
There was one damage, even for pretend play.
オッケー わかった
Okay.
なんで君達の攻撃のほうが私のより強いの？
Why are your attacks stronger than mine?
わぁ ボスにしてはすいぶん弱いね？
Wow, you're pretty weak for a boss, aren't you?
いや 違う 子猫ちゃんには ちょうどいいくらいのダメージを出してるよ ははは！
And no, she does the right amount of damage for a kitten. Ha ha ha!
消えろ！ 死ね！
Die! Die!
あぁ わかった もうやめて
Oh. Okay, you can stop.
オッケー うん…ていうか私って本当にボスなの？
Okay. Um, am I really the boss?
なんで君たちが私の敵なの？私はただ家に帰りたいだけなのに
Why are you two my enemies? I just want to go home.
なんか急にやばそうだよ！ うう… あああ……
Something suddenly feels really bad! ddyahhuuuu uaaaa...
私の後ろに隠れて 大丈夫 私が受け止める え 何？何これ？
Stand behind me. It's okay, I'll tank it. The? What? What is this?
魔法が…急に溢れ出してる！
Magic is suddenly... coming out on its own!
ねぇ やめて！そういう意味じゃなくて！ ダメ！うわっ！
Okay. Don'! Why did you take it that way? No, BAD! Argh!
私 本当にあいつらに勝っちゃった
I actually beat them!
え 今のだったの？
Oh. What was that just now?
私って本当にすごい…？ めちゃくちゃ強いんだ
Am I... Am I just really goated? I'm really strong.
でも なんで勝手に起きたの？
But why did it happen on its own?
勝ったけど……甘やかしてくれる人がもういない
I won, but now there's nobody left to pamper me.
unhappy?
if you're dealing with a lotta woes
unlucky?
then you gotta listen very close
be happy!
keep on trying, never give up
don't forget that you're alive
the past you have been running from
that boring future yet to come
still counseling you oh my, oh my
universal peace, peace yeah
unhappy? unlucky? be happy! undead, oh
hey, hey, hey, hey
somehow feeling like there's a fight within
and it's been going on so long
i don't feel it and don't even wanna try
past version of me, of me, of me, of me
and those figures of the old
transparent ghosts over my route
the childish and painful memories have the deepest roots
saddening? nowhere to be seen
say what? way better then? irony
Say what? Way better than? Irony.
they all see the me of the past when looking at me now
nonsense label i can't erase yes!
in essence, a complex
it's almost like something's possessing me
it is wrapping tight around and won't loosen its bounds
the self i used to be before undead, oh still alive
time is a chain of your own path
to be alive is to always embrace your inner changes, on and on
don't settle for unhappiness don't be complacent in distress
not even trying to seize the joy and be happy, you coward
oh, this world, oh, this world is one odd, one odd fantasy
who knows what is coming up next, a monster or a snake?
this is a story starting after that encounter, finally
(Unhappy?)
If you're dealing with a lotta woes
(Unlucky?)
Then you got to listen very close
(Be happy)
Keep on trying, never give up
(Undead, oh)
Don't forget that you're alive
The past you have been running from
That boring future yet to come
Still counseling you, oh my, oh my
Universal, peace, peace yeah
Unhappy?
Unlucky?
Be happy
Undead, oh
Hey, hey, hey, hey, somehow feeling like
There's a fight within and it's been going on so long
I don't feel it and don't even wanna try
Past version of me and those figures of the old
Transparent ghosts over my route
The childish and painful memories
Have the deepest roots
(Saddening?) Nowhere to be seen
(Say what?) Way better then? Irony
They all see the me of the past when looking at me now
(Nonsense) Label I can't erase
(Yes) In essence, a complex
It's almost like something's possessing me
It is wrapping tight around and won't loosen its bounds
The self I used to be before (undead, oh)
Still alive, time is a chain of your own path
To be alive is to always embrace your inner changes, on and on
Don't settle for unhappiness, don't be complacent in distress
Not even trying to seize the joy and be happy, you coward
Oh, this world, oh, this world is one odd, one odd fantasy
Who knows what is coming up next, a monster or a snake?
This is a story starting after that encounter, finally
With people or monsters and spirits, back on topic, peace, peace yeah
Past and future
Can't change the past
Run for the future
ああああああああああああああ
Ah...
あなた
You
わたし
And I,
ふたりぼっち
all alone together...
みらい
Future,
どこへいこっか
where should we go?
悲しみが壊れそーだ
Sadness is about to break,
星空に泣き声が響くのさ
and cries echo through the starry sky.
ああああああああああああああ
Ah...
ひろいせかい
In this vast world,
なにをうたおっか
what should we sing about?
悲しみがあふれて泣きそーだ
Sadness overflows, almost making us cry,
握りしめたその手が冷たくて
and the hand I tightly held is so cold.
ああああああああああああああ
Ah...
悲しみが壊れそーだ
Sadness is about to break,
星空に泣き声が響くのさ
and cries echo through the starry sky.
悲しみがあふれて泣きそーだ
Sadness overflows, almost making us cry,
君の声が彼方に消えていく
and your voice fades away into the distance.
ああああああああああああああ
Ah...
I turned both of them into undead...
I thought I'd finally been reunited with my friends, too.
And now I'm all alone in this gloomy place.
Hm? What's this?
My name... HP...
Oh, I've seen these. I've seen these.
Wait, I love this. Okay. Let's see. What does it say?
Okay. Kronii. Like sleep. Yeah. Okay. That makes sense.
Oh, pet play...?
Oh, what? Since when did I become a pet? I'm not even into those.
I should be the owner. Not that I'm into that to begin with,
but, oh, that's-- that's scary. It's like someone's weird fantasy got mixed in here. That's not mine.
Oh, okay. And there's even a keyword for recording the story.
Uh, everyone watching this, make sure to use that keyword when you document it and share it with other people, okay?
Well. And, oh, yeah. Another thing.
That magic from earlier?
I know you guys are the ones giving the commands.
What kind of person would make me cast something like that at my friends?!
But it was really powerful, wasn't it?
Oh, it completely caught me off guard.
Oh, with magic like that, I can beat anybody.
And even if I could, I wouldn't wanna use it on my friends. That would suck.
Oh, I wonder how I'm supposed to get back home.
I just want to eat someone's cooking already!
Oh, and I've been trying my best, so I want everyone to praise me, too. Meow!
I'm crashing out.
Oh, if I'm the boss of this place, that means-- that means I can sit in that throne, right?
Oh, that's so cool. Wait. I'm so excited!
Okay. Well, for now, I'm just going to sit in the chair and take a break. Yeah. Okay.
WELCOME TO THE MIND FXXK
まてよ そこ行く娘さん 逆子宿らせ
Hold on a second, young lady with that baby in your belly
あどけない足らない そんな身体に
And that body with so little innocence left
正しく回らん 愚図の頭で
Is that stupid, pathetic little brain of yours
天真爛漫！？ほざくな馬鹿め。
Thinking you're so naive and pure? Get a grip, you fool!
まちな そこ行く兄さん 何の片割れ？
Hold on a moment, sir. What kind of scum are you?
小さなあの娘の 御花を咲かせ、
Now that you've plucked that little girl's precious flower
指きりげんまん 星の彼方へ
And promised her the moon, you're taking to your heels?
陽関三畳！？くたばれ雑魚め。
Leaving her with a few casual words?! Go to hell, you asshole!
「いついつ出やるの？かごめよかごめ」
"When, oh when is it coming out? Pregnant girl, oh pregnant girl."
嫌味をからげて 笑うあなたへ
Just some cheap "sympathy" born from between the sheets, for you, my dear—
誰もがやがては 地獄の底へ（連れて行かれる）
In the end, everyone shall end up in the bottom of hell (They'll all be dragged down there.)
ぴたりと重ねて 吐き出す情け
Though you certainly seem fond of that cynical, mocking attitude
あー、触れあって 埋めあって 勝ち取った 幸せを 盗られた正義のヒーローが泣いている
Alas, the hero of justice is crying, now that the happiness he fought so hard to gain—
抱きあって 叩きあって 分かち合った あの頃を忘れてしまえたら
After some mutual fondling and fulfilling—has been taken from him
どれほど楽だろうか
How much easier it would be if only he could forget those moments of much embracing, fighting, and sharing
WELCOME TO THE MIND FXXK
擦り切れた肌かさぶた 枯れた山河 愛しさ交えて 痛む片腹 またまたわがまま ばっかなまさか？
Scraped skin full of scabs. Incredible points of pleasure. Such ridiculousness, with a hint of lovingness.
まだまだ長々 長ばなな か？
Don't tell me, you're falling back into that silly, i-want-everything-my-way mode? Looks like you've still got a lot to learn!
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
Okay
たちまち 独壇場
a one-man show,
Listen listen
片向け 振り切れろ
Let's shake it off.
ヤーヤーヤーヤーヤーヤーヤー ショウタイム
Yah-yah-yah-yah-yah-yah-yah, show time!
天辺の御成り ほらおいでの
Behold the summit's grand arrival, come over now,
宵をコンプリート オーライ
complete the night, alright!
だんだんノリノリで超簡単 Brah Brah Brah !!! Pow
Getting pumped up, it's super easy, brah brah brah, pow!
えも言われえない
It's beyond words,
Ain't nobody stop
全堂絢爛豪華 Attention 騒がうか
The realm shines in stunning splendor, attention, let's make some noise!
意思表示にまじき衝撃の音声 高らか堂々登板
Soon, comes an impressive debut with a voice of impact!
もう伽藍堂はとくのとう滔々だ
The empty shrine has long been eradicated.
Aye 爛漫桜花 お出ましだ
Aye, cherry blossoms madly bloom, behold the grand arrival!
強がったって 嘘はばれるぞ
Even if you act tough, lies will be exposed.
怖がったって 血は流れるぞ
Even if you're scared, blood will flow.
黙ったって 傷口開くぞ
Even if you stay quiet, wounds will open.
嫌がったって 傷は痛むぞ
Even if you hate it, wounds will hurt.
じゃれあって 眺めあって 語りあった あのときを
Those times we joked around, watched each other, and talked...
思い回しては 悲観に暮れてみる
Reflecting on them, I drown in grief.
駆け寄って 寄り添って 笑い合った あのときを
Those times we ran up, snuggled close, and laughed together...
いっそきれいに 忘れてしまいたいんだ
I'd rather forget it all cleanly.
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
Okay 立ちまち 独壇場 Listen listen
Okay, one-man show, listen listen!
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
天辺の御成り ほらおいでで
Behold the summit's grand arrival, come over now!
宵をコンプリート オーライ
Complete the night, alright!
だんだんノリノリで超簡単 Brah Brah Brah !!! Pow
Getting pumped up, it's super easy, brah brah brah, pow!
えも言われえない Ain't nobody stop
It's beyond words, ain't nobody stop!
全堂絢爛豪華 Attention 騒がうか
The realm shines in stunning splendor, attention, let's make some noise!
意思表示にまじき衝撃の音声 高らか堂々登板
Soon, comes an impressive debut with a voice of impact!
もう伽藍堂はとくのとう滔々だ
The empty shrine has long been eradicated.
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
万歳 遊ぶ気にことぶき Shout it out, Shout it out
Hooray, rejoice in the spirit of delight, shout it out!
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
ハニナリ 感情通りに発想飛び Shout it out, Shout it out
Elegantly soaring, let emotions guide, shout it out!
食らっちゃいな
Eat it up!
Rat a tat a tat a tat
Rat tat tat tat tat!
満開総員 一気に飛び切り Jump around Look at me now
Full-bloom, all at once with full force, jump around, look at me now!
皮膚を破りそうなほどに跳ねる心臓くらい 激情的好様 (Exotic vox)
Passionately intense specification, almost like a heart pounding fiercely through the skin!
イニミニマニモ ご来場からのご来光
Eeny-meeny-miny-moe, the view of the sunrise upon a pre sense!
かくれんぼしてるその気持ち解放 (理性に向かって)
Set free the elusive feeling that's been playing hide and seek!
じゃらばだびがっ取るにまわまいやしんかしつつようなジュース たぶらかすな なっちや
Becoming reckless, a dual-faced deception, got the juice that makes me jealous, don't play tricks!
じゃらばだびがっ取るにまわまいやしんかしつつようなジュース たぶらかすな なっちや 十色のバタフライ
Before reaching karma, colorful butterfly, no escape!
ご存じのとおり 想像しき鼓動に 負かされてもう止まれない
As you know, bounded by the noisy heartbeat, I can't stop anymore.
衝動に塗装し 描いた Daybreak
Daybreak painted with impulsive hues.
はい 貫通 低音 強
Maddening bass tones piercing through the lungs.
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
イチかバチか Aa
It's all or nothing, ahh!
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
万歳 遊ぶ気にことぶき Shout it out, Shout it out
Hooray, rejoice in the spirit of delight, shout it out!
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah, Ready for my show
巻き起こすために
To stir things up,
喧嘩上等 Shout it out!
Ready for a fight, shout it out!
Hey yeah...
右に左まとめて 暴れ出す
Rounding up right and left, breaking loose
思いっきり 鳴らせ
Ring it out with all your might,
鳴り止わぬ衝動 Shout it out!
an unceasing impulse, shout it out!
駄目 駄目 駄目
No, no, no,
脳みその中から「やめろ馬鹿」と喚くモラリティ
my morals scream from my brain, "Stop it, idiot!"
ダーリン ベイビー ダーリン 半端なクラブと きらめき浮き足立つフィロソフィ
Darlin' baby darlin', a half-assed club and a philosophy with giddy, restless feet
死ぬほど可愛い 上目遣い なにがし法に触れるくらい
So adorable when looking up at me, enough to break some law
ばら撒く乱心 気づけば蕩尽 この世に生まれた君が悪い
Scattering madness, squandering it before I knew it, you're to blame for being born into this world
やたらしんどい 恋煩い バラバラん頭とこの身体 頸動脈からアイラブユーが噴き出て
So agonizingly lovesick, my head and body torn apart, "I love you" spewing from my carotid artery
アイリス アウト
Iris out,
一体どうしよう この想いをどうしよう 暴れの奥を ザラメが溶けてゲロになりそう
What on earth should I do with these feelings, deep inside the sugar crystals melt and I feel like barfing,
瞳孔 バチ開いて 溺れ死にそう 今この世で君だけ大正解
pupils wide open, about to drown to death, in this world right now you're the only absolute right answer
ダーリン ベイビー ダーリン ダーリン ベイビー ダーリン
Darlin' baby darlin', darlin' baby darlin'
ひっくり返しても勝ちようない 君だけルールは適用外 四つともオセロは黒しかない 勝ち上がりたい
Even if I flip it over I can't win, rules don't apply to you, all four othello discs are black, I want to rise up,
君が笑顔で放った アバダケダブラ デコにスティグマ 申し訳ねえな 矢を刺して 貫いて ここ弱点
You smiled and cast Avada Kedavra, a stigma on my forehead, my bad, pierce me with an arrow, run me through, here's my weak spot,
死ぬほど可愛い 上目遣い なにがし法に触れるくらい ばら撒く乱心 気づけば蕩尽 この世に生まれた君が悪い
So adorable when looking up at me, enough to break some law, scattering madness, squandering it before I knew it, you're to blame for being born into this world,
パチモンでもいい 何でもいい 今君と繋がってる全て欲しい 頸動脈からアイラブユーが噴き出て
Fake is fine, anything is fine, right now I want everything connected to you, "I love you" spewing from my carotid artery,
アイリス アウト
Iris out,
一体どうしよう この想いをどうしよう 暴れの奥を ザラメが溶けてゲロになりそう
What on earth should I do with these feelings, deep inside the sugar crystals melt and I feel like barfing,
瞳孔 バチ開いて 溺れ死にそう 今この世で君だけ大正解
pupils wide open, about to drown to death, in this world right now you're the only absolute right answer,
ダーリン ベイビー ダーリン ダーリン ベイビー ダーリン
Darlin' baby darlin', darlin' baby darlin',
カエラ！
Kaela!
クロニー！やっと知ってる人に会えた！
Kronii! Finally, someone I know!
私もだよ〜！
Yeah, me too!
ここどこなの？
Where even are we?
帰りたいのに帰れないの
I wanna go home, but I can't...
私も帰れなくて困ってたんだけど
Well, I've been stuck here too, and couldn't find a way back.
もう帰れないなら 楽しむしかないと思うんだよね
But if we can't leave, I figured we might as well enjoy ourselves.
すぐ前向きだけど
You know, that's a pretty positive attitude, but...
ここから帰りたくないの？
don't you wanna go home?
帰りたいよ？
Of course I do.
そういえば
Well, you know, come to think of it,
君はここで何をしてるの？クロニー？
what are you doing here, Kronii?
なんかここのボスらしくて ここから出られないの
So, apparently, I'm some kind of boss here, and I can't leave this place.
甘やかす人もいないし
And there's nobody around to spoil me either...
おや、甘やしてほしいの？
Oh, you want someone to spoil you?
なら私がよしよししてあげるよ
I can give you some head pats, if you like.
Heh...
ほんと？
Really?
あなたはそれでいいの？
You're okay with that?
もちろん！おいで！おいで！
Yeah, sure! Come here! Come here!
にゃ〜！
Meow!
私もボスだったけど誰も来なくて
I was a boss too, but nobody ever came to see me.
寂しいからこの世界から出たかったんだ
I got lonely, so I wanted to leave this world.
寂しかったからここを離れたかったの？
You wanted to leave because you were lonely?
わ私はね ジジとセシリアと戦うことになって 何が起きてるのかさっぱり分からなかったのに
I, I ended up fighting Gigi and CC, and I had no idea what was going on.
まぁ 私のところには人が来なくて探検しに来たんだ
Well, nobody came to my place, so I decided to go exploring.
そうだ！私とも戦ってくれる？楽しそう！
Alright! Will you fight me too? It sounds fun!
ちゃんと聞いてないよね…
You aren't really listening are you...
戦いだって楽しんだもん勝ちだよ！
A battle is only fun if you enjoy it!
いくよ！
Here I come!
いったいどうしちゃったの？
What's wrong with you?
私の武器はハンマー！
So my weapon is a hammer.
いくよ！
Here I come!
やぁ！
Hya!
適当にあしらって終わらせようかな
Maybe I'll just humor her and get this over with.
本気でやらないとおもしろくないよ！
It's no fun if you don't take it seriously!
本気出したらやっつけちゃうでよ！
But if I do, I'll end up defeating you!!
大丈夫 大丈夫！ほら来い！
It's fine, it's fine. Come on, hit me with it.
いけ！
Hit it.
知らないからね
Well, don't say I didn't warn you.
おおー！！！
Ohooo...!!!
ほら言ったでしょ
Yeah. See, I told you.
めっちゃやばかった！
That was awesome!
本当にすごいね！
That was amazing!
いや すごいのはあなただよ！
Oh, you're the amazing one!
いや〜楽しかった
Well, that was fun.
この世界なんかついといて 歌って踊って 楽しい時間を過ごして帰ろう！
So let's stop worrying about this world, sing, dance, and have a good time before we head home!
歌って踊るのはいいけど ちょっと突然すぎない？
I'm fine with the singing and dancing part, but isn't this a little sudden?
しかも どうやって帰るつもりなの？
And how exactly are you planning on getting us home?
あぁ… わかんない！
Well... I don't know!
純情ハート？ 知らんよ
Pure heart? I don't know.
恋愛 知らんよ
Romance? I don't know.
それおいしいの？ っておいしいのってな
Is it yummy? Hey, is it yummy?
ランボだめだめ 感情奈落に投げ込んだ
Violence, stop it, throw feelings into the abyss!
いっせーので丸ごとぶっ飛ばせ
Ready, go, and blow it all away!
混沌ブギウギ ハッピー追加サービス
Chaos Boogie Woogie, happy extra service!
出しちゃえよ出しちゃえってほら！
Bring it out, bring it out, hey!
脳細胞が消えてくｗｗｗｗ
My brain cells are disappearing lmao!
いっせーので死に至るまで踊れ
Ready, go, and dance until you drop!
三千大千の世界だ
In this vast and endless world,
碌に死になんてありえない
you can't just easily die.
三千大千の果てた
At the edge of this infinite world,
方がいいかな
maybe it's better that way.
我がままばかりじゃ傷つかない
Being selfish won't hurt anyone,
噂がで過ぎて気持ち悪い
rumors spread so much it makes me sick.
当たり前のことも手に付かないもん なんて辛い
Even the simplest things are out of reach, how painful.
世界中でとか投げ出したい 狂ったように泣き出したい
I want to throw it all away, crying out like I'm crazy.
思うがまま生きて消えていきたいな
I want to live as I please and fade away.
純情ハート？ 知らんよ
Pure heart? I don't know.
恋愛 知らんよ
Romance? I don't know.
それおいしいの？ っておいしいのってな
Is it yummy? Hey, is it yummy?
ランボだめだめ 感情奈落に投げ込んだ
Violence, stop it, throw feelings into the abyss!
いっせーので丸ごとぶっ飛ばせ
Ready, go, and blow it all away!
混沌ブギウギ ハッピー追加サービス
Chaos Boogie Woogie, happy extra service!
出しちゃえよ出しちゃえってほら！
Bring it out, bring it out, hey!
脳細胞が消えてくｗｗｗｗ
My brain cells are disappearing lmao!
いっせーので死に至るまで踊れ
Ready, go, and dance until you drop!
ワンツーまさかリ三四しっかり取り戻いんだってもういんだって
One, two, what do you know! Three, four, reap what you sow...
ハッピーよ代わり gift me ときめき一斉のでさあ飛び込め
Happy replacement gift me, ready go and jump right in!
本能ブギウギ混沌ぞくもりもいんだってもういんだっても
Instinct Boogie Woogie, chaos is in full swing...
最低ヤスラロライカミステリー一斉のでぶっ飛ばせ
The lowest-tier Leica mystery, ready go and blow it all away!
混沌ブギウギハッピー追加サービス出出しちゃえよ出しちゃえってほら！
Chaos Boogie Woogie, happy extra service, bring it out!
だんだん落ちてく人生クソワロ一斉ので死ぬまで踊れ
Slowly falling apart in this crappy life, dance until you drop!
もういいや全部全部ほら忘れ去ってしまおう
Forget it all, let's just leave it behind.
簡単なことじゃないが我々ならできるだろうな
It's not easy, but people like us can do it.
踊ろうぜ
Let's dance!
頭でわかって嘆いた 転がしていく様子を嘲った
Knew it already, sighing at how things roll.
寂しいとか愛とかわかんない 人間の形は投げ出したんだ
Don't know love or loneliness, I threw away human form.
抱えきれない 言葉だらけの存在証明を
This proof of existence filled with words I can't hold.
この小さな劇場から出られない 気づいたら最後逃げ出したい
Trapped in this small theater, wanting to escape before I notice.
僕ら全員演じていたんだ エンドロールに向かっていくんださ
We were all just acting, heading toward the end roll.
まあ皆必死に役を演じて 傍観者なんていないのさ
Everyone acts for their lives, there are no bystanders.
ワタシなんてないの どこにだっていないよ
There is no "me," nowhere to be found.
ずっと僕は 何者にもなれないで
I could never become anyone at all.
僕ら今ささ 喰らい合って 延長戦サレンダーして メーデー
Now we bite at each other, surrendering into overtime, Mayday!
淡い愛想 垂れ流し 言の愛憎
Spilling shallow affection, words of love and hate.
ドラマチックな展開をどっか期待してんだろう
Hoping somewhere for a dramatic turn of events.
君も YES YES 息を呑んで 采配はそこに有んだ ヘッドショット
You too, holding your breath, headshot where the command lies!
騒ぐ想いも その心抉り抜いて さあ まだ見ぬ糸を引いて 黒幕のお出ましさ
Piercing through that heart, pulling unseen threads, here comes the mastermind!
その目に映るのは
What reflects in those eyes...
触れたら壊れてしまった
Touched, and it broke apart,
間違ってく様子を黙った
and watched silently as things went wrong.
僕ら全員無垢でありました
We were all completely innocent,
いつのまにかやら怪物になったんだ
but before we knew it, we became monsters.
その全てを肯定しないと前に進めないかい
Can we not move forward without affirming all of it?
『まあ君にはきっと無理なんだ』
"Well, it's surely impossible for you,"
いつのまにかやら外野にいたんだそんなガヤばっかり飛ばしてきたんだ
before we knew it, we were on the sidelines, just tossing noise around.
皆必死に自分を守って救いの手を待ってるのさ
Everyone is desperately protecting themselves, waiting for a helping hand.
考えたくはないよ馬鹿になっていたいも
I don't want to think, I just want to play the fool.
ずっと僕は何者にもなれないで
I've always been unable to become anybody.
だから今
So right now,
前線上に立って
standing on the front line,
その旗は高く舞って
that flag dances high,
劣勢 頼る相棒
in an underdog plight, relying on a partner—
言葉すらいらないよ
we don't even need words.
ドラマチックな展開はどっとヒットしてんだろう
A dramatic turn of events must be hitting home,
君も yes, yes 息を呑んで再会を誓い合って
you too, yes, yes, holding your breath, swearing to meet again,
ワンチャンスしかないもっと一生懸命なのさ
giving our all for our one and only chance—
クライマックスみたいな手に汗を握るのさ
gripping our hands in sweat like a climax.
ぽつりと鳴いた
It cried out with a plop,
隠してきた真実はどこにもない
The truth we've kept hidden is nowhere to be found,
喋ってきた奴らに居場所はない
and those who spouted it have nowhere to belong.
思い出してぽいってして感情はない流した涙理由なんてない
Tossed aside from memory, with no emotion—the tears we shed have no reason.
優しさに温度も感じられない
We can't feel warmth in kindness,
差し伸べた手に疑いしかない
and can only doubt the hand that is extended.
穴が空いて愛は垂れてしまいたいなったんだ
A hole opened up and love spilled out,
倒れそうな僕を吸い込んだんだ
swallowing up my collapsing self.
諦めかけた人の前にアンタはいつも嘲笑うようにお出ましさ
Right before someone ready to give up, you always show up with a jeering smile.
君にはどんな風に見えてるんだい呼吸を整えてさ
How does it look to you? Calm your breathing—
ずっと僕は何者にもなれないで
I've always been unable to become anybody.
僕ら今さっきさくらい合って
and right now, biting at each other in a battle of attrition,
延長戦サレンダーしてメーデー
surrendering in overtime, Mayday!
淡い愛想垂れ流し泥の愛憎
Spilling faint affability, muddy affection and hatred—
ドラマチックな展開をどっか期待してんだろう
expecting some dramatic turn of events somewhere.
君も yes, yes 息を呑んで采配はそこにあんだ
You too, yes, yes, holding your breath, the orders are right there.
ヘッドショットもう思いもその心撃ち抜いてさ
Headshot! Strike through those swirling thoughts and that heart right now—
まだ見ぬ糸を引いて黒幕のお出ましさ
pulling unseen strings, the mastermind makes an appearance.
“その目に映るのは”
"What reflects in those eyes—"
都合の良い思いを燃やして
Burning up convenient thoughts,
呆れた願いはもう手放した
I've already let go of this absurd wish.
裏切りや秘密が漂ってここから動けない
Betrayal and secrets linger, and I can't move from here.
生まれてしまった、あるいは壊れすぎてしまった
Born like this, or perhaps broken beyond repair,
あの日あの場所でずっと、止まったままだった未来
that future remained stuck at that place on that day.
それでも、心のどこかで君を感じていた
Even so, somewhere in my heart, I felt your presence.
許せない、今の僕は誰？
Unforgivable—who am I right now?
ねぇ、ずっとずっとそばにいたんだ
Hey, you were always, always by my side.
「勘違いだ」って、嘘じゃないよ
It's no misunderstanding, that's no lie.
望んだものではなくともあなたに出会えた痛みだけが愛だと信じられるように
Even if it wasn't what I hoped for, so I can believe that only the pain of meeting you is love—
僕に触れないで！祈る、セレナーデ
don't touch me! I pray, serenading.
僕なしでうまく幸せになってね
Be happily successful without me,
誰よりずっと、何を手放しても
more than anyone, no matter what I let go of.
これが愛だと信じていた、罰をください
I believed this was love—give me my punishment.
誰でもない、あなた あなただけ
Nobody else, only you, just you.
世界がまだ忘れてくれなくても
Even if the world still won't forget us,
きっと、まだ あなた あなただけ
I'm sure, still you, only you.
願い疲れても歌うよ、セレナーデ
Even tired of wishing, I'll sing, serenading.
シナリオ通りのコメディ不幸自慢はハウメニー？
A comedy following the script, how many boast of misfortune?
エゴイスティックに光った瞳の中に映っている
Reflected in eyes shining egoistically,
「あなた」は「誰？」闇が光らせた舞台の上で
"'You' are 'who?' on the stage illuminated by darkness."
希望も不幸も身勝手だ僕らは、全員共犯者だった
Both hope and misfortune are selfish; we were all accomplices.
疑う余地もないほど
With no room left to doubt,
運命が定まった、あの夜から僕は愛し方を忘れた
ever since that night when fate was sealed, I forgot how to love.
これだけ願って、これだけ祈って
Wishing only this, praying only this,
こんな、悲しい結末でごめんね
sorry for such a sad ending.
すべて失って、すべて消え去っても
Even if I lose everything, even if everything vanishes,
ただ、君がずっと生きていた痛みが欲しい
I just want the pain of you having lived on.
あと何回数えたら、あと何回傷つけば
How many more times counted, how many more times hurt—
光に包まれ
Wrapped in light,
永い時間を過ごし
spending a long time,
想い出す事も多くなったかな
I wonder if I've come to remember more things.
このミライ あのミライも全て
This future, that future, all of them
奮い起こされて
Roused up,
今が動き出す
now things begin to move.
新たなミライへと
Toward a new future.
踏み出せば手を取った
If I stepped forward, you took my hand,
まだ先は長いんだと
Wishing that the road ahead was still long,
願ってくれた
You hoped for me.
歩み続ける事
Continuing to walk,
もう何回も もう何回も
many times, many times,
重ね合わせた音は
the sounds we layered together
読み込まずとも 深く焼き付いて
are deeply burned in without needing to load.
記憶の片隅 既視感
A corner of memory, déjà vu,
想いのシンクロニシティ
synchronicity of feelings.
どのミライも離さないで
Don't let go of any future,
今、始めよう
now, let's begin.
慈しむ声が 優しいあの歌が
The affectionate voice, the gentle song,
巡り巡って 愛は伝わってく
revolving and revolving, love is transmitted.
感情線は走り出す
Emotional words start to run,
追いかけていくから 追いかけさせるから
because I'll chase you, because I'll make you chase me,
熱を帯びて 時を駆けて
taking on heat, running through time,
君に届け 交わる今想いのMemory
reach you, intersecting now, the memory of feelings.
覚えてる?
Do you remember?
出逢ってから いつも君が隣に
Ever since we met, you've always been by my side,
ずっと情熱は冷めない 鮮やかなまま
passion never cools down, remaining vivid.
好きな事好きな様に そんな場所だから
Doing what you like, the way you like, because it's such a place,
物語は紡ぎ結ばれた
the story was spun and connected.
君とのキセキをLoading
Loading the miracle with you.
Kronii!
I've come to save you!
I knew it, Subaru-senpai!
How'd ya I needed help?
I've been watching the whole time!
The whole time...?
And me?
I watch you.
Oh, okay.
That's scary, but... why?!
I, I wish you helped me a lot sooner then!
Well, you started having fun halfway through,
so I figured I'd see how things played out!
Yeah.
I watched... just the world.
Okay. Yeah. Oh, the world. Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, I guess I did end up enjoying parts of it.
See?! That's why I was wondering whether you actually needed saving!
Aw... well thank you, I guess,
but can you really help me get out of here?
Just... please wait.
Just one more song. If you sing and dance your heart out, you can go home!
Really? Yay!
Just watch the world! The world!
Oh, so that's the world. Oh, okay.
Wait, wait. Sorry. I was so fascinated. Please staff, please staff, down, up, up, up, up, up, up. Yeah, yeah!
Really?!
Kaela disappeared after fighting and singing, right?
That's because she went back to the original world.
After fighting and singing?
Wait, does that mean I have to fight too?
Yep! Oh...
覚えてる?
Do you remember?
出逢ってから いつも君が隣に
Ever since we met, you've always been by my side,
ずっと情熱は冷めない 鮮やかなまま
passion never cools down, remaining vivid.
好きな事好きな様に そんな場所だから
Doing what you like, the way you like, because it's such a place,
物語は紡ぎ結ばれた
the story was spun and connected.
君とのキセキをLoading
Loading the miracle with you.
泣いて笑ったミライ
A future of crying and laughing,
手をつないで歩もう
let's walk holding hands,
これこれからも
from now on as well.
彩る生命が 創り上げた今が
The now created by coloring life,
不可能を可能に 機能を現実に
making the impossible possible, making functions a reality,
木漏れ日生い茂る青の葉
green leaves where sunlight through the trees thrives,
君と眺めていた 愛の砂時計
the hourglass of love we gazed at together.
熱を帯びて 時を駆けて 君に届け
Taking on heat, running through time, reach you,
交わる今キセキのMemory
intersecting now, the memory of miracles.
ほら 君も共に奏でよう
Come on, you too, let's play together,
愛を込めても込めきれないくらい
to the extent that even with love poured in, it can't be poured enough,
麗しい想い 狂おしい程ぎゅっと
beautiful feelings, tightly hugging to the point of madness.
もっと あと もう ちょっと
More, after, just a little more,
きっと 君のミライになるから
because it will surely become your future.
ヒカリに包まれ 永い時間を過ごし
Wrapped in light, spending a long time,
手に入れた物は 掛け替えの無いmemory
what I obtained is an irreplaceable memory.
叫んだ世界(あなた)が大好きだ
I shouted, "I love the world (you)!"
両手一杯のミライは重なる
A future filling both hands overlaps,
熱を帯びて 時を駆けて 君に届け
taking on heat, running through time, reach you.
運命は今 ここで
Destiny is right here now,
鳴り響け 願いを 込め付けて 世界に 届け
ring out, put your wish into it, reach the world,
輝く今 ミライのmemory
the shining now, the memory of the future.
見るだけで幸せになるでしょ？
Just looking at it makes you happy, right?
うん、まあ、すごく可愛いけど、
Yeah. I mean, it's very adorable, but...
私もここにいるんですけど、にゃ～、にゃ～、にゃ～
I'm also right here too. Meow, meow, meow...
クローニィもマジで可愛い！
Kronii is super cute, too!
でも、でも、これは、これ何？
But, but, this is... What is this?
シャイ・クローニィ？
Shy Kronii?
違います！やめてくださいよ～！
No, stop! No, stopppppp!
クローニィはにゃーなの？
Is Kronii a cat?
私、私は…それでいいです
I-I-I's fine. If you don't know, then never mind.
ちょっと怖すぎるよ、クローニィ！
That's way too creepy, Kronii!
ねえ！なんで？！
HEY, what's that mean?!
今日のクローニィはちょっと、ちょっと大丈夫かな？大丈夫？
Today Kronii is a little, little are you okay? Are you okay?
私は大丈夫じゃないけど、そんなこと言わないで！ていうか、戦うんですよね？
Hey, that's... I'm never okay. But you shouldn't say that! Anyway, aren't we supposed to fight though?
うん、よし！
Yeah. All right!
スバ友、大丈夫？
Subatomo, are you okay?
いけ！スバ友！
Go Subatomo!
よし！攻撃！行け行け行け行け！
Yeah! Attack! Go go go go go!
おまえー！！
You!!
来い！戻れ戻れ戻れ戻れ！大丈夫？
Come! Back back back back! Are you okay?
なんか…ちょっと弱いかーも、ウィークかもこいつ
Subatomo... might be a little underwhelming... This lil guy's a weakling.
さぁ、そろそろ準備しようかな。全然痛くない、ぐすぐったくない、ごめんね～
Well, I guess I should start getting prepared. It doesn't even hurt. Not even tickle. Sorry.
やばいぞ！やばい！
This is bad! Really bad!
スバ友！！うぇ…うぇ…私たちは受ける！この場を一緒に！やばい！やばい！やばい！
Subatomo! We're taking this one together! Oh no! Oh no! Yabai! Yabai!
もう身代わりだよお前が！
...no more here, alright!
プリーズ、プリーズ、マージ！プリーズ、マージ！
Please, mercy! Please, mercy! Please!
いくよー！わぁあああ！
Here I go... Waaaah!
わぁあああ！そんなあ、やってないよ…
Waaaah! That's terrible...
イェーーイ！ごめんね、でもイェーーイ！
Yayyy! I'm sorry, but yayyyyy!
スバ友ーーー！大丈夫かスバ友！おいしょ、よいしょ
Subatomo-----! Are you okay, Subatomo!
おお、生きてる よかった。大変だった
Oh, it's alive, oh thank god, okay. That was rough.
ほら、楽しんでるでしょ！たぶんこれで家に帰れるはず！
See? You're having fun! This should probably get you home now!
頑張って！
Good luck!
イェー！ありがとう！
Yeah! Thank you!
バイ！
Bye!
帰ろう！スバ友！気をつけてねー！バイ！
Go home, Subatomo! Take care of everything! Bye!
なんだだったんだろう…
What was that...
何が起きているのかよくわからないけど、どうやら最後にもう1曲歌えば家に帰れるみたい。じゃあ、やってみよう
I don't really get what's going on, but apparently I can go home if I sing one last song. So let's do that.
待って、これなに？
Wait. What's this?
なに？うんうん、上から順番に1つずつ見てみようか。何かの役に立つかもしれないし
What? Okay, okay. Let's go through them one by one from the top. Maybe they'll be useful for something.
これは私の周年を記念したグッズってことだね。さて、何があるんだろう？
So these are the merch celebrating my anniversary, hey? Let's see. I wonder what they've got.
どれも結構使えそうだから、一緒に見ていこう。まずは、バケットハット
They all seem pretty useful, so let's check it out together. First up, we got a bucket hat.
イラストははまなし先生に描いてもらいました。
The illustration was done by Hama Nashi sensei.
コンセプトは私が…みんなの予想通り！ラスボス！リバーシブル仕様でイラストも
The concept is me being... you guessed it! The final boss! It's reversible and the artwork looks
すっごくかっこいい！たぶんなんとなくだけど防御力も上がりそう気がするし
really cool! And maybe it would make you feel like it would boost your defense stat!
続いては、と、ランダム属性アクリルキーホルダー！ちびキャラはGurin先生に描いてもらいました
And next up, we got a random attribute acrylic keychain. The chibi characters were drawn by Gurin sensei!
どれが出るか楽しみだね！えへ！そしてアクリルキーホルダーの次は～クッションです！
I wonder which one you'll get, hey, hey? And after the Acrylic Keychain, we got a cushion!
デザインでこれはもGurin先生に描いてもらいました！両面にイラストが入っていて、サイズ感も使いやすいクッションです
The design for this was also done by Gurin sensei. The cushion has an illustration on both sides, and size wise, it's pretty easy to use as well.
次は、可愛いボロスランプです！明るさを2段階で調整できて、デザインもすっごく可愛い！
Next up, we got this cute Boros Lamp! Looks like you can adjust the brightness between two levels, and the design is super duper cute.
暗い場所でも安心だね。怖い時もボロスがいてくれるよ。みんな心配しないで！
You'll be safe even in dark places. When you're scared, he's got you. Don't worry everyone.
そして次は…！シチュエーションボイスパック！タイトルは「悪役クローニィのラストループ」
And coming up next, we got a situation voice pack! The title being "Villainess Kronii's Final Loop."
何だか不穏なタイトルだけど、聴くのが楽しみ！早くチェックしたいな
Sounds pretty ominous, but... I can't wait to check it out. I want to check it out.
If you purchase everything, you'll also receive a cheki-style card
with a foil stamped signature,
along with a bonus voice pack.
The card illustration was drawn by,
you guessed it, Hama Nashi sensei!
And as for the bonus voice pack, it's going to be telling the story of
joining hands and heading into the final battle in order to bring the loop to an end.
It's going to be very emotional, so go check it out.
Once more, here is the full line-up. Yeah!
Every single one of these looks like they'd help me escape this other world,
so I definitely want to get them all.
And, with that, looks like that's everything.
So, according to Subaru senpai,
all I have to do is sing one more song.
So... whew, here goes. Let me try it.
,s:
The streets are enlivened as the evening settles in
and the winds carry away the flock of crows and people
,s:
there is no meaning, just life itself
just being hungry, I get back home to you
,s:
As I grew up, I'd look up and suddenly realize
everyone in this world starts from two people
,s:
What's deep in my heart, what will fade away someday
It is to be by your side, always remember it
,s:
What you have inside, the heartbeat in the distance
I fell in love with your laced fingers and scent, going beyond husband and wife
,s:
The feelings once thought ugly begin to take on colors
And swans carry them away, changing what is taken for granted
,s:
I cannot help falling in love with similar faces and fiction
Love is born from one person
,s:
What's deep in my heart, what will fade away someday
It is to be by your side, always remember it
,s:
What you have inside, the heartbeat in the distance
I fell in love with your laced fingers and scent, going beyond husband and wife
,s:
Your crying face, the night of silence
And your wavering smile, forever and ever
,s:
What's deep in my heart, what will fade away someday
It is to be by your side, always remember it
,s:
What you have inside, the heartbeat in the distance
I fell in love with your laced fingers and scent, going beyond husband and wife
,s:
Go beyond two people, go beyond one person
ここはどこ…？
Where am I...?
戻ってきた！
I'm back!
それとも寝てただけ？ 全部夢だったの？
...or was I asleep? Was it all a dream?
わからないな
I dunno.
あぁ 私も歳かな
Oh, I'm getting old.
ほんと変な体験だったな
That was such a weird experience.
あ そうだ！ 誰か家に呼ぼうとしてたんだった！
Oh, yeah. I was going to invite someone over to my place.
それで 何か食べるものを作ってもらおうとして…
And then I was going to ask them to make me something to eat.
あ 待って 違う 私まだ偉そうだな
Oh, wait. No, I'm still being arrogant.
お願いじゃなくて命令じゃん
That's not asking. That's giving an order.
まあ 命令して当然だけどね～
Which damn right I should.
いや もっと優しく言わなきゃ
No, I should be nicer about this.
ご飯を作って にゃ～
Make me some food, please. Meow~
うんうん そう これが可愛いね
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's... That's cute.
いや そうでもない みんなどうするつもりなの
Or not. What are they going to do?
あ ごめん 長い1日だったの とにかく…
Sorry. Been a long day. Who am I even talking to? Anyway...
うん わかんない 誰を家に呼ぼうかな？
Yeah. Yeah, I don't know. Who should I invite?
こんな時間に誰か来てくれる人いるかな？
Is there going to be someone around at this hour?
よし ちょっと考えよう
I gotta think about this...
あ？！なにかこれえぇーーー！！
Oh, what the fu----!!
Reincarnated as a Villainess?!
I Reincarnated as a Villainess?! Ouro Kronii 4th Anniversary LIVE